<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Test feed]]></title><description><![CDATA[Thoughts, stories and ideas.]]></description><link>http://site.com/</link><generator>Ghost 0.5</generator><lastBuildDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2015 22:27:30 GMT</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://site.com/rss/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><ttl>60</ttl><item><title><![CDATA[The £1,000,000 Bank-Note (by Mark Twain)]]></title><description><![CDATA[<h1>The £1,000,000 Bank-Note</h1><p>When I was twenty-seven years old, I was a mining-broker's clerk in San Francisco, and an expert in all the details of stock traffic. I was alone in the world, and had nothing to depend upon but my wits and a clean reputation; but these were setting my feet in the road to eventual fortune, and I was content with the prospect.</p><p>My time was my own after the afternoon board, Saturdays, and I was accustomed to put it in on a little sail-boat on the bay. One day I ventured too far, and was carried out to sea.</p><p>Just at nightfall, when hope was about gone, I was picked up by a small brig which was bound for London. It was a long and stormy voyage, and they made me work my passage without pay, as a common sailor.</p><p>When I stepped ashore in London my clothes were ragged and shabby, and I had only a dollar in my pocket. This money fed and sheltered me twenty-four hours. During the next twenty-four I went without food and shelter.</p><p>About ten o'clock on the following morning, seedy and hungry, I was dragging myself along Portland Place, when a child that was passing, towed by a nurse-maid, tossed a luscious big pear - minus one bite - into the gutter. I stopped, of course, and fastened my desiring eye on that muddy treasure.</p>]]></description><link>http://site.com/1000000_bank_note_en/</link><guid isPermaLink="false"></guid><category><![CDATA[Mark]]></category><category><![CDATA[Twain]]></category><category><![CDATA[Bank-Note]]></category><dc:creator><![CDATA[Mark Twain]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2015 17:47:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Банкнота в миллион фунтов (Марк Твен)]]></title><description><![CDATA[<h1>Банкнота в миллион фунтов</h1><p>Когда мне было двадцать семь лет, я работал служащим у маклера горной промышленности в Сан-Франциско и знал все тонкости дела. Будучи одиноким в этом мире, положиться я мог лишь на свою сообразительность и непорочную репутацию. Я находился на пути к возможной удаче и был вполне доволен.</p><p>По субботам, после полудня, я посвящал время исключительно себе. У меня вошло в привычку плавать в бухте на небольшой лодочке. Однажды я осмелился выйти слишком далеко в море.</p><p>Упали сумерки, а с ними, казалось, была потеряна последняя надежда, когда вдруг меня подобрало маленькое судно, направляющееся в Лондон. Наше плавание было долгим, а погода штормовой. Я выполнял обязанности рядового матроса, чтобы как-то оплатить свой проезд.</p><p>На берег в Лондоне я сошёл в потрёпанной и изношенной одежде и с единственным долларом в кармане. Эти деньги кормили меня и давали мне приют в течение суток. Следующие двадцать четыре часа я провёл без еды и крова.</p><p>Около десяти утра следующего утра, слабый и голодный, я брёл вдоль Портлэнд Плэйс. Со мной поравнялась гувернантка, волоча за собой упирающегося ребёнка, который неожиданно швырнул огромную соблазнительно-сладкую, но едва надкушенную грушу в канаву. Естественно, я тут же остановился, устремив свой взгляд на это, уже валявшееся в грязи, сокровище.</p>]]></description><link>http://site.com/1000000_bank_note_ru/</link><guid isPermaLink="false"></guid><category><![CDATA[Mark]]></category><category><![CDATA[Твен]]></category><category><![CDATA[Банкнота]]></category><dc:creator><![CDATA[Марк Твен]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2015 17:47:01 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>
